Fear will drag you deeper.
Quicksand is a thriller, horror, mystery film directed by Andres Beltran.
A married couple on the brink of divorce becomes trapped in
quicksand while hiking through a Colombian rainforest.
It’s a struggle for survival as they battle the elements of the
jungle and must work together in order to escape.
Sofia, played by Carolina Gaitán.
Josh, played by Allan Hawco.
Marcos, played by Sebastián Eslava.
Diego, played by Andrés Castañeda.
Front Desk Clerk, played by Allison Castrillón.
Concierge, played by Juan Manuel Combariza.
Spellbound is a 2024 American animated musical fantasy comedy film directed by Vicky Jenson from a screenplay by Julia Miranda and
the writing team of Lauren Hynek and Elizabeth Martin, based on a story conceived by Jenson, Hynek, and Martin.
It features music composed by Alan Menken, who also wrote the songs
with longtime collaborator and lyricist Glenn Slater.
Produced by Skydance Animation, the film features the voices of Rachel Zegler, John Lithgow,
Jenifer Lewis, Tituss Burgess, Nathan Lane, Javier Bardem, and Nicole Kidman.
Set in the world of magic known as Lumbria, the story follows Princess Ellian (Zegler) who must break the
spell that has turned her parents (Bardem and Kidman) into monsters and split her kingdom in two.
The project, initially titled Split, was announced in July 2017, shortly after Skydance Animation
was formed in March 2017, with Paramount Pictures scheduling distribution for 2019.
The film subsequently underwent changes, such as release dates, with Jenson later announced as the director, and
the film's title changed to The Unbreakable Spell, before eventually getting to its current title.
The film was acquired by Apple TV+ in December 2020, before
Netflix took over the rights in October 2023.
Much of the main voice cast signed on in June 2022,
following Zegler's casting in April 2022.
Production was done remotely during the COVID-19 pandemic.
Spellbound premiered at the Paris Theater in New York City on November
11, 2024, and was released via Netflix on November 22.
It received mixed reviews from critics.
The tone is mind_bending and dark and emotional.